<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
   
   	<title>RealJenius.com - Tag: police</title>
   
   <link>http://realjenius.com</link>
   <description>I'm a software developer in the game industry, and have been (for better or worse) coding on the Java platform for the last decade. I also do all my own stunts.</description>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <managingEditor>R.J. Lorimer</managingEditor>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   
	<item>
  <title>What may happen to your laptop when you come to Israel?</title>
  <link>http://realjenius.com/misc/2009/12/15/what-may-happen-to-your-laptop-when-you-come-to-israel.html</link>
  <author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
  <pubDate>2009-12-15T00:00:00+08:00</pubDate>
  <guid>http://realjenius.com/misc/2009/12/15/what-may-happen-to-your-laptop-when-you-come-to-israel.html</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[
     <p>Check out this <a href="http://lilysussman.wordpress.com/2009/11/30/im-sorry-but-we-blew-up-your-laptop-welcome-to-israel/" target="_blank">I’m sorry but we had to blow up your laptop</a> story. Israeli security officers shot through the girl’s laptop with three bullets because she was suspected due to some of ‘suspicious’ pictures in her camera and an arabic phrasebook, a journal entry that mentioned a Palestinian, stamps from Syria, Qatar and the UAE, Palestinians in Palestine guidebook, and a map with a main street in Jerusalem, the central bus station and hostel. They didn’t shot through the hard disk though .. lol</p>

<p>When I was in Saudi, I have seen an European guy who stayed in the same hotel with my colleague got arrested by a group of police officers in front of me while he was taking picture of stray cats (nearby a govt. building). The guy later said that they searched through his camera and all of his stuffs, deleted all the pics and questioned him for the whole day. Quite scary.</p>

<p><img src="http://lilysussman.files.wordpress.com/2009/11/p1070617.jpg?w=650" alt="" /></p>

<p><img src="http://lilysussman.files.wordpress.com/2009/11/p1070618.jpg?w=650" alt="" /></p>


  ]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>