<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
   
   	<title>RealJenius.com - Tag: wordpress</title>
   
   <link>http://realjenius.com</link>
   <description>I'm a software developer in the game industry, and have been (for better or worse) coding on the Java platform for the last decade. I also do all my own stunts.</description>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <managingEditor>R.J. Lorimer</managingEditor>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   
	<item>
  <title>Powered by the buggy WordPress!</title>
  <link>http://realjenius.com/headlines/2009/11/28/powered-by-the-buggy-wordpress.html</link>
  <author>R.J. Lorimer</author>
  <pubDate>2009-11-28T00:00:00+08:00</pubDate>
  <guid>http://realjenius.com/headlines/2009/11/28/powered-by-the-buggy-wordpress.html</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[
     <p>As you may notice that vnsecurity.net server has been taken offline since the beginning of last week for the server upgrade. Our new server has a much better HW specs compare to the old one.</p>

<p>We’ve also replaced the great Plone/ZODB/Python with the buggy WordPress/Mysql/PHP for our website. I myself really like the Zope Workflow and Zope Object Database with the great fine-grained access control but many members doesn’t like Plone and it’s a bit slow especially on a few years old HW with only 1GB RAM (there were 03 Plone’s instances running for vnsec, vnsecon and vithon.org websites which used all of the 1GB memory).</p>

<p>I don’t trust PHP &amp; PHP Apps. WordPress/PHP, with a massive number of security bugs in the past, makes me feel unsafe :). Secunia has a good list of <a title="WordPress 2.x Vulnerabilities" href="http://secunia.com/advisories/product/6745/" target="_blank">WordPress 2.x vulnerabilities</a> and 07 bugs are still unpatched.</p>

<p>But on the other side, WP has some really nice plugins and themes which save my time. It’s like replacing the great &amp; responsible old lady babysitter to a new sexy but “dangerous” young college girl. I hope that some additional protection layers and access restriction to the backend would help to save my a$$ from WP’s bugs.</p>

<p>Cheers!</p>

<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-25" title="Babysitter___comic_by_TwinTwosGirl" src="http://www.vnsecurity.net/wp/storage/uploads/2009/11/Babysitter___comic_by_TwinTwosGirl.png" alt="Babysitter___comic_by_TwinTwosGirl" width="540" height="911" /></p>

  ]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>